(Arthur:)Like I'm 75 again.
(Leonard:)Oh, God.
(Arthur:)What... what is it?
(Leonard:)Sheldon just sent me a picture of him
and Bill Nye getting smoothies.
(Arthur:)-Can I ask you a question?
-Yeah, sure.
(Arthur:)Why do you put up with Sheldon?
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Leonard:)You know, because we're friends.
(Sheldon:)Why?
(Leonard:)Wow, you ask really hard questions.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)Look, I know he can be aggravating,
(Leonard:)but what you have to remember is that
he's not doing it on purpose.
It's just how he ls.
(Leonard:)But he's also loyal and trustworthy
(Leonard:)and we have fun together.
(Arthur:)You know you're describing a dog.
(Leonard:)He did bite me once.
But in his defense, I came up
behind him while he was eating.